{
    "subject": "resource/Ministry_(band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Ministry (band) is the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9410352110862732,
            "question": "Is Ministry (band) a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9368151426315308,
            "question": "Ministry (band)'s hometown is located where?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8483911752700806,
            "question": "What country is Ministry (band)'s hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6952230334281921,
            "question": "Where is Ministry (band) from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5542429685592651,
            "question": "Where did Ministry (band) originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266108512878418,
            "question": "What is the home country of the band Ministry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5136950612068176,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Ministry (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44318583607673645,
            "question": "Ministry (band) is based in which nation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4165804982185364,
            "question": "In what country was Ministry (band) formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33059316873550415,
            "question": "Which country claims Ministry (band) as its own?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Ministry (band) is the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9306_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was Ministry (band) formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9306_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ministry (band) is based in which nation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9306_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Ministry (band)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9306_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9306_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Ministry is an American band, they don't specify that their hometown is the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that Ministry, an American industrial metal band founded in Chicago, Illinois, which is in the United States. Therefore, it supports the statement that the hometown of Ministry (band) is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that Ministry was founded in Chicago, Illinois.  Chicago is a city in the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}